Guide to the Eva Overton Lewis and Julian Herman Lewis, MD, PhD Collection circa 1887-2015
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Eva Overton Lewis Papers
  - Subseries 2: Correspondence
    - Letter – Cordelia O. Lewis to Eva Lewis, April 21, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Letter – Eva Lewis to Eleanor Wheatland, July 16, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Letter – Esther Popel Shaw to Eva Lewis, August 20, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Letter – M. A. Southwick to Eva Lewis, circa August 1926 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Note – Eva Lewis to Theta Omega sorority about roses received and feelings about going abroad, circa 1926 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Letter – Berthe and Jeanne dressmaker to [Gloria] Julienne Lewis, September 15, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Letter – Cecelia Roane to Eva Lewis, November 3, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Letter – Anthony Overton to Eva Lewis, November 4, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Letter – Anthony Overton to Eva Lewis, November 14, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Card – Esther Popel Shaw to Eva Lewis, December 1926 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Letter – Anthony Overton to Eva Lewis, December 23, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Letter – Gloria Lewis to Eva Lewis, circa 1926-1933 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Letter – J. Blondin to Eva Lewis, circa 1927 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Letter – Louise Young [neé Lewis] to Eva Lewis, circa 1927 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Letter – [Louise Young?] to Eva Lewis, January 8, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Letter – Mr. Chandler to Eva Lewis, January 10, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Letter – Mabel Overton Fowler to Eva Lewis, January 14, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Letter – Anthony Overton to Eva Lewis, January 21, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Letter – Eva Lewis to Cordelia O. Lewis, February 28, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Letter – Cecelia Roane to Eva Lewis, March 1, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Letters – Eva Lewis to Cordelia O. Lewis, April 8, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Letter – Eva Lewis to Cordelia O. Lewis, May 3, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Letter – Anthony Overton to Eva Lewis, May 7, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Letter – Eva Lewis to Vesta Lewis, May 2, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Letter – Robertann B. [Cuthbert?] to Eva Lewis, May 21, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Letters – Eva Lewis to Cordelia O. Lewis, July 21-28, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Postcards – Cordelia O. Lewis to Eva Lewis, July 24-30, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Postcard – Geraldyn [?] to Eva Lewis, September 4, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Card – Laura Smith to Eva Lewis, December 16, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Letter – Felicia Alexander to Eva Lewis, June 25, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Letter – Cordelia O. Lewis to Evan Lewis, May 2, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Letter – Gloria Lewis to Eva Lewis, June 11, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, June 25, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Letter – Louise Young [neé Lewis] to Eva Lewis, June 29, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Envelope – Anthony Overton to Eva Lewis, July 1931 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Letter – Cecelia Roane to Eva Lewis, July 14, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Card – Helen and Malcolm [?] to Eva Lewis, August 6, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Cards – Cordelia O. Lewis to Eva Lewis, August 24-27, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Letters – Gloria Lewis to Eva Lewis, circa August 1931 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Letters – Julian H. Lewis, Jr. to Eva Lewis, circa August 1931 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Letters – Lewis children, Julian Lewis, and Cordelia O. Lewis to Eva Lewis, August 20-September 6, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Letters – Cordelia O. Lewis to Eva Lewis, September 13-24, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Letters and drawing – Gloria Lewis to Eva Lewis, September 22-30, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Card – Lewis children to Eva Lewis, September 28, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Letter – Louise Young [neé Lewis] to Eva Lewis, September 15, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Letter – Cecelia Roane to Eva Lewis, October 22, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Letters – Cordelia O. Lewis to Eva Lewis, October 22-28, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Letter – Helen Dibble to Eva Lewis, October 19, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Letter – M. Hill to Eva Lewis, October 23, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Envelope – To Mrs. Richard Hill, November 23, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Letter – Anthony Overton to Eva Lewis, November 5, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Letter and clipping – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, November 5, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Letter – Cordelia O. Lewis to Eva Lewis, November 12, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Letter – Gloria Lewis and Cordelia O. Lewis to Eva Lewis, November 23-25, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Letter - Louise Young [neé Lewis] to Eva Lewis, circa November 1931 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Cordelia O. Lewis to Eva Lewis, December 4, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Card – Gloria, Julian Jr., and John Lewis to Eva Lewis, December 15, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Letter – [Louise Young?] to Eva Lewis, circa 1931 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Letter – Eva Lewis to Maurice Stamps, circa 1931-1932 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Letter – Cordelia Lewis to Eva Lewis, June 4, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Letter – George Ellis to Eva Lewis, June 30, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Letter and questionnaire – Chicago Tuberculosis Institute to Eva Lewis, November 3, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Postcard – Warren Roane to Eva Lewis, circa 1942 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Letter – John Calhoun Lewis to Eva Lewis, March 30, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Postcard – Eva Lewis to Clara Vesta Caldwell (née Lewis,) August 20, 1943, Sent from Idlewild, Michigan (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Envelope – Julian Lewis, Jr. to Eva Lewis, July 14, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Letter – Anthony Overton to Eva Lewis, August 25, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Series III: Lewis Family Papers
  - Subseries 1: Cordelia O. Lewis
    - Letter – John Calhoun Lewis to Cordelia O. Scott [Lewis], 1889 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Telegram – Joe Evans to Cordelia O. Lewis, May 8, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Envelope – U.S. Department of State, Passport Division to Cordelia O. Lewis, March 11, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Letters and receipts – Temple Tours, Inc. to Cordelia O. Lewis, January-May 1927 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Cunard Entertainment Program, June 3, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Travel itinerary, July 1927 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Thomas Cook and Son, Paris and London – Travel itinerary and coupons, August 1927 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Souvenir booklet, “William Tell: The Legend of the Forest Cantons,” 1927 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Subseries 2: John Calhoun Lewis
    - Letter – H. Gideon Wells to John Calhoun Lewis, circa 1915 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Subseries 3: Lynn Lewis
    - Letter – Mollie [?] to Lynn Lewis, September 15, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Subseries 4: Anthony Overton
    - Letter – H. A. Turner to Anthony Overton, June 10, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Douglass National Bank of Chicago invitations, 1922 and 1923 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Douglass National Bank cancelled check, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Travel itinerary, October-November 1926 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis, Jr. to Anthony Overton [?], circa August 1931 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Clipping – Naming of school for Anthony Overton, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Anthony Overton biographical information, 1993-2010 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Chicago Bee Building preservation and renovation, 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Memorial program for Anthony Overton III with notes, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Subseries 5: Gloria Lewis
    - Letter – Cordelia O. Lewis to Gloria Lewis, February 14, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Letter – Cordelia O. Lewis to Gloria Lewis, May 7, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Letter – Cordelia O. Lewis to Gloria Lewis, June 1921 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Postcard – Cordelia O. Lewis to Gloria Lewis, February 1923 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Valentine cards to Gloria Lewis, February 1929 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Letter – Gloria Lewis to “Sis,” circa August 1931 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Royal Coterie of Snakes debutante ball certificate, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Subseries 6: Julian H. Lewis, Jr.
    - Postcard – Cordelia O. Lewis to Julian Lewis, Jr., February 12, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis, Jr. to “Uncle Dick and Aunt Frank,” circa August 1931 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis, Jr. to Oscar [?], circa August 1931 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Subseries 7: Lewis Family Ephemera
    - Booklet – “Pocket Rules for Leading at Whist…,” 1897 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Christian Science pamphlets, 1908-1913 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Postcards – University of Illinois, Strauch's Student Life Series, circa 1910s (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Letter – Henry White and Sons to B. Muro and Co., 1912 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Postcard – Recreation Pier, Chicago [Navy Pier], circa 1916 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Soldiers' French Phrase Book, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Wedding certificate, guest list, gift list, and card, September 1918 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Marriage announcement – Julian and Eva Lewis, September 1918 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Baby Book, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Eloise Carey Bishop calling card and note, circa 1920s (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper clippings, circa 1920s (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Cards and postcard to Gloria Lewis, 1921, 1923, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Pathé of France Ltd “Baby” Projector manuals, circa 1922 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Douglass National Bank statements and cancelled checks, 1924-1926 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Meat Market receipt, circa 1925 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - List of names, circa 1926-1933 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Receipts, 1926-1934 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Drawing – Margot Delande, circa 1927 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Invoice – Cours de l'Étoile, Rue de la Néva, March and June 1927 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Checks stubs, 1928-1940 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Isabel King piano recital program, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Sarah Merchant piano recital program, Michigan Avenue Community Hall, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Change of address form, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Piano recital programs – Gloria Lewis and Julian Lewis, Jr. at Michigan Avenue Community Hall, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Cordelia O. Lewis obituary – Cairo Evening Standard clipping, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Life and disability insurance, 1933-1934 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Insurance bill, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Subscriptions, 1933-1934 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Caterina Jarboro recital program, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Seth Thomas Clock Co. instructions, circa 1934 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Utility bills, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Leon Kirkpatrick piano recital program, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Englewood High School graduation program, Gloria Lewis and Julian Lewis, Jr., 1938 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - “The Family Bible Teacher” issues, circa 1940s (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Newspaper clippings, circa 1940s (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Business and calling cards, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Envelop – Dr. Carl G. Roberts, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - “Guide Posts in the Bible,” undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Ink blotter, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Notes – Feeding and medicine schedule, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Notes – Monthly expenses [?], undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Subseries 8: Lewis Family Correspondence
    - Envelope – To Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, circa 1916 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Overton [Lewis], September 10, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis to Eva Overton [Lewis], September 10, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, March 25-29, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, April 5-13, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Letter – Louise Young [née Lewis] to Julian Lewis and Evan Lewis, May 10, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Letters – Eva Lewis to Julian Lewis, June 4-14, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, June 5-8, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Letter – Cordelia Lewis to Julian Lewis, August 26, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, August 23, 1922 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, April 16, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Envelope – To Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, August 11, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Marriage announcement, Elizabeth Wolf and Lionel Blitzsten, August 11, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Telegram – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, December 31, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Letters – Eva Lewis to Julian Lewis, May 9-29, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, May 21-27, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Letters – Eva Lewis to Julian Lewis, June 3-9, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, June 1926 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Bon Voyage Reception invitation, August 11, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, August 24-31, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Telegram – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, August 31, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Bon Voyage cards, circa 1926 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Bon Voyage notes, circa 1926 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Bon Voyage telegrams, August -September 1926 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Postcards – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, August-October 1926 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, September 3-8, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Telegram – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, October 9, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, October 18-30, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Letter – Unidentified writer describing travel [Anthony Overton?], circa October 1926 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Letter – Eva Lewis to Julian Lewis, circa November 1926 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, November 9-29, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Letter – Chandler Owen to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, November 3, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, circa November-December 1926 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, December 13-22, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Letter – Cordelia O. Lewis to Eva Lewis and Julian Lewis, December 12, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Postcards – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, 1926-1927 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Postcards – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Letter fragment – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, circa 1926-1933 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Telegram, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, January 14-25, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, Cordelia Lewis to Julian Lewis, George Ellis to Julian Lewis, February-March, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, February 9-15, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis and Dr. Dailey to Julian Lewis, February 20 and March 2, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, March 3-23, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Telegrams – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, March 18-19, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, April 1-3, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Telegram – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, April 16, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Telegram, April 16, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, May 3-28, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Telegram – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, May 12, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Telegram – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, circa 1927 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, June 2-28, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, July 1927 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, circa November 1927 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Card – E. H. Morris family to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, December 17, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, circa 1930-1942 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, circa 1930s (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Letter – Helen Lewis to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, May 14, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Invitation - Chicago Normal College commencement, June 26, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, July 9-15, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Postcards – Gloria Lewis and Julian H. Lewis, Jr. to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, July 23, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, August13-27, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Letters – Cordelia O. Lewis to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, August 2-23, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Letters – Cordelia O. Lewis to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, August 19-December 13, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Cards – To Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, September 3, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Letter – Cordelia O. Lewis to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, September 3, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, September 12-18, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Wedding invitation – Sidney F. Graham to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, October 29, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Letter – Cordelia O. Lewis to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, November 22, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Letter – Gloria Lewis to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, December 18, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Letter – Cordelia O. Lewis to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, February 21, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Letter – Louise Young [née Lewis] to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, June 29, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Telegram – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, March 25, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, June 25, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Letters – Eva Lewis to Julian Lewis, June 18-28, 1934, Sent from Idlewild, Michigan (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, July 10, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, August 1934 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, August 2, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Letter – Louise Young [née Lewis] to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, April 14. 1942 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, circa 1942 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Letter – Ruth [?] to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, September 2, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Letter – Elizabeth Neil to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, September 10, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Envelope – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, July 21, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Letters – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis and children, August 5, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Letters – John Lewis to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, August 23, 1944, Sent from Idlewild, Michigan (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, August 28, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, July 19, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis and John Lewis, July 29, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Letter – Julian H. Lewis, Jr. to Julian Lewis and Eva Lewis, July 25, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, August 15, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Letter – Julian Lewis to Eva Lewis, undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Envelope addressed to Dr. Carl G. Roberts, undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Envelope addressed to Felicia Alexander, undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Subseries 9: Travel ephemera
    - French and Italian business cards, circa 1920s (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Académie Nationale de Musique et de Danse – Souvenir program, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Folies-Bergère advertisement featuring Josephine Baker and “Fowler and Tamara,” circa 1926 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Notice to Bearers of Passports, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Passport Regulations, Temple Tours, circa 1926 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Railroad and ship tickets, 1926American Express travelers checks book, circa 1926-1927 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Clothing receipt – Kaller, Basel, circa 1926-1927 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Heim, Paris advertisement, circa 1926-1927 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Hotel ephemera, 1926-1927 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - List of names – “Correspondence,” circa 1926-1927 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Notebook – French, circa 1926-1927 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Paris apartment leases, 1926-1927 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Passenger ship ephemera, 1926-1927 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Receipts, Paris, 1926-1927 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Restaurant, café, and nightclub ephemera, 1926-1927 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Souvenir guidebooks, 1926-1927 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Flyer – “Wagon-Restaurant a ce train,” circa 1926-1927 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - List of prices or fees, circa 1926-1929 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Luggage stickers, circa 1926-1929 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Advertisement – “Chopin ou le Poète,” by Guy de Pourtalès, circa 1927 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Allgemeine Musikgesellschaft Basel concert program, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Bills, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Clipping about Josephine baker – “La Rose Noire,” circa 1927 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Hirschwaldsche Buchhandlung documents, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Invitations, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - José Iturbi concert advertisement, April 1927 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Pen and ink drawings by E. Kunz of scenes in Basel, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Program – Salle de l'Étoile, Paris – “Audition Musicale et Séance Récréative des Élèves du Cours de l'Étoile,” March 1927 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Ticket stubs, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - “Rosemary from gardens of Pompeii and sliver of wood from the house of one of the Kings of Pompeii,” undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 10: Photographs and Audiovisual Materials
    - Tintype – Unidentified infant, circa 1880s-1900s (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Photograph – Cordelia O. Scott [Lewis], studio portrait, circa 1887 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Photocopy of photograph of John Calhoun Lewis, circa 1890s (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Carte de visite – Julian H. Lewis, Clara Vesta Lewis, and Louise Lewis, circa 1894-1895 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Photograph –Anthony Overton, studio portrait, circa 1890s-1900s (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Photographs – Unidentified children, circa 1890s-1910s (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Photographs – Unidentified people, circa 1890s-1910s (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Photograph – Cordelia O. Lewis, studio portrait, circa 1897-1907 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Photographs – Eva Overton [Lewis], circa 1900-1905 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Photograph – Geraldyn Major, studio portrait, circa 1900-1910s (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Photograph – Richard Hill, studio portrait, circa 1900-1910s (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Photograph – Richard Hill, reproduction of studio portrait, circa 1900-1910s (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Photographs – Unidentified people, circa 1900-1923 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Photograph – Julian H. Lewis, studio portrait, 1902 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Photographs – Lewis Marion Young, studio portrait, circa 1905 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Photograph – Cordelia O. Lewis, studio portrait, circa 1905-1910 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Photograph – Eva Overton [Lewis], circa 1906-1911 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Photograph – Julian H. Lewis in uniform, circa 1908 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Photograph – Eva Overton [Lewis], circa 1908-1911 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Photographs – Julian H. Lewis with graduating class, circa 1909 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Photographs – Anthony Overton, circa 1910s (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Photographs – Eva Overton [Lewis] swimming and sitting on sand dunes, circa 1910s (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Photograph – George W. Walker, signed, circa 1910s (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Photographs – Group photos including Eva Overton [Lewis] – University of Chicago botany class?, circa 1910s (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Photographs – Julian H. Lewis and Eva Overton [Lewis] standing on lakeshore dunes, circa 1910s (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Photograph – Mabel Overton, circa 1910s (Box 9, Folder 4)